威尔 · 森坦斯: 现在，我们几乎就要进入最后的冲刺阶段了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Now, we're getting
towards the final stretch, almost.
所以，在这里，我们有它，我们有我们的美好分享,
So, here, we had it,
we had our wonderful shared,
我们的函数和对象的单一保存版本。
single saved version of our function and
our objects.
用户1、用户2、用户500[ SOUND ]都可以通过原始链接访问它。
User 1, user 2, user 500 [SOUND] all had
access to it through the proto-chain.
不通过原型引用作为 JavaScript 原型的结果,
Nope, through the proto-reference, as
a result of JavaScript prototype nature,
它的原型特征，它的对象连接到其他对象的能力。
its prototype feature, its ability for
objects to connect to other objects.
所以，当我们没有在给定的对象上找到一个函数时，不要惊慌，直接向上。
So, when we don't find a function on
the given object, don't panic, head on up.
好的，现在，我想做一些有趣的事情，没有奖金。
Okay, now, I wanna do something
interesting here, no bonus.
如果我想确认一下呢，顺便说一下，没有什么改变
What if I want to confirm,
nothing's changed by the way, except for
现在我没有使用增量。
now I'm not using increment.
我正在使用这个方法，这个函数具有 ownproperty。
I'm using this method,
this function hasOwnProperty.
如果我们想要确认我们的用户1拥有属性分数怎么办？
What if we wanna confirm our
user1 has the property score?
这很有趣，hasOwnProperty 在这里。
This is interesting, hasOwnProperty here.
我假设 hasOwnProperty 在 user1上是一个属性，Matt，是吗？
I presume hasOwnProperty is on
user1 as a property, Matt, is it?
扬声器2: 是的，我的意思是，那里没有什么可以用的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes, I mean,
there's nothing there for it.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没有财产，对不起,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There's no property,
sorry,
没有叫做 hasOwnProperty 的方法，没错。
no method called hasOwnProperty,
yeah, exactly.
它一定在用户功能商店里，是吗，托德？
It must be on user function store,
is it Todd?
演讲者2: 不，不是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, it's not.
那么这个函数从哪里来呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So
where is this function gonna come from?
人们发现，在 JavaScript 中有一个很大的标题对象,
It turns out people, that there is a big
old headline object in JavaScript,
稍后我们会看到它的确切存放位置,
we're gonna see exactly where it's
stored a little bit later on,
但是现在，威尔 · 森塔斯: 有一个很大的古老的
but for now
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There's a big old
在 JavaScript 中称为 object.prototype 的标题对象。
headline object in JavaScript
called object.prototype.
我们稍后会了解更多，就是这样。
We're gonna learn more about that
a little bit later, there it is.
说实话，我应该换个颜色。
I should do it in a different color,
honestly.
但是我要，而不只是一种，和
But I'm gonna, instead just kind of, and
它有很多有用的功能，亲爱的。
it has a bunch of useful functions
that are gonna be available to, dear.
我们所有的对象都可以使用。
They're gonna be available
to all of our objects.
但是怎么做呢？
But how?
因为，你不会相信的。
Well because, hey, you won't believe it.
但是 JavaScript 中的所有对象，不仅仅是用户1和
But all objects in JavaScript,
not just how user 1 and
用户2，我们在这里设置我们的原始值,
user 2, where we set our proto value,
的所有对象都有一个 proto 属性。
all objects in JavaScript
have a proto property.
一个默认的，默认链接到，你想猜猜马特在哪里？
A default one, that defaults to linking
to, you wanna take a guess to where Matt?
说话人2: 对象 Will Sentance: To this object.prototype
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The object
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: To this object.prototype
对象。
object.
我可能不会去画那支箭，对吧？
I'm not gonna probably draw the arrow,
am I?
但是让我们做一个小星星。
But let's just do a little star.
这个用户函数存储将链接到这个对象。
This user function stores is
gonna link down to this object.
那个物体的原型你猜里面有什么 Matt？
The object.prototype object, and
what do you bet's in there, Matt?
你猜里面有什么功能？
What function do you bet's in there?
讲者二: hasOwnProperty。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: hasOwnProperty.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 哈森有房产，他说对了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: hasOwnProperty,
he's spot on,
有自己的财产，我猜超级有用。
hasOwnProperty, super useful I guess.
这样，当我运行 user1.hasOwnProperty 时,
Such that,
when I run user1.hasOwnProperty,
然后用 scores 作为我的论据来执行。
and execute it with score as my argument.
凯拉，我在哪里找用户1？
Kayla, where do I look for user 1?
讲者3: 在全球。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: In global.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 在全球化中我会找到它吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In
global will I find it?
是的。
Yeah.
然后在该对象上查找 hasOwnProperty。
Then I look for
hasOwnProperty on that object.
我在用户1上找到它了吗？
Do I find it on user 1?
讲者3: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 绝对不是，不是那里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Definitely not,
not there.
我恐慌吗？
Do I panic?
原型性意味着解释器会去哪里
Where does JavaScript prototypal nature
mean that the interpreter is gonna go and
看下一个，到？
look next, up to?
讲者3: 用户功能-威尔 · 森特斯: 太棒了,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The user function-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
也许有房子在这里。
maybe hasOwnProperty's here.
是增量，是不。
Is increment, is No.
我们恐慌吗？
Do we panic?
不，我们去看看，我们要看什么隐藏财产，凯拉？
No, here do we go look, what hidden
property that we're gonna look at, Kayla?
演讲者3: 原型。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The prototype.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 原始财产，是的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The proto property,
yeah, yeah.
别担心，我们会看到区别的，但是原始属性(proto property)是指向-的链接
Don't worry, we'll see the difference, but
the proto property, which is a link to-
讲者3: 反对，普罗托。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Object.proto.
那么我们在那里发现了什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And
what do we find there?
讲者3: hasOwn。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: hasOwn.
Will Sentance: hasOwnProperty，我们抓取它的代码，然后执行它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: hasOwnProperty, and
we grab its code, and we execute it.
我们实际上在做的就是控制我们的目标
What we're actually doing with our
object.create is kinda taking control
我们在那个原型里放了什么。
of what we put in that proto.
因为默认情况下所有对象，它们的原型,
Because all objects by default,
their proto,
一旦他们被创建，就会得到一个到 object.prototype 的链接。
as soon as they're created gets
a link to object.prototype.
我们已经控制住了，但是不要惊慌，我们不会失去访问权
We'd have taken control of that, but
don't panic, we don't lose access
这里的东西，因为它是一个链，所有的方式。
to this stuff down here,
because it is a chain all the way up.
我想说的是,
To the point that I kinda
want to show the line,
只是想让你知道这是个链条，对吗？
just so you know it's a chain, right?
这是一个链条，威尔 · 森坦斯: 这是一个链条
It's a chain,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's a chain all
一直到我们的头条，反对，原型。
the way up to our headline,
Object.prototype.
这个对象还有一个原型属性。
This object also has a proto property.
不，但是不要惊慌。
No, but don't panic.
如果有人猜的话，我会告诉你们链条的顶端。
Anyone take a guess given this is, I'm
just gonna tell you the top of the chain.
这对原始人来说有什么价值？
What this might have as its value for
proto?
丹？
Dan?
讲者二: 未入籍人士。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Under naturalised.
是的，非常接近，但是没有，是的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
actually very close but null, yeah,
就像我们现在结束了一样，没有更高层了，好吗？
it's like we're done now,
there's no further up the chain, okay?
但是我不打算详细说明，但是如果你这样做的话
But I'm not going to go into this in
greater detail than that, but if you do
想知道所有复杂的细节，就去看面向对象的硬件部分。
wanna know all the intricacies of that,
go watch the object oriented hard parts.
真的[笑]或者人们对此的谈论,
Really [LAUGH] or people's talks on that,
我们会讲得更详细。
go parts on that,
we go into in much more detail.
特别是关于数组和函数如何也有大量的集合
Especially related to how arrays and
functions also had a big collection of
他们可以使用与此相关的共享函数。
shared functions they
can use related to this.
好吧，还有一件事我想说。
Okay, there is another thing
I want to talk about though.
是的，如果你想确认我们的用户有属性分数呢？
Yes, what if you wanna confirm our
user's has the property score?
我们可以使用 hasOwnProperty 方法。
We can use the hasOwnProperty method.
但是它在哪里呢？
But where is it?
在用户1上吗？
Is it on user 1?
不，我们所有人默认都有一个原型属性
No.
All of us have a proto property by default
默认导向一个大物体 object.prototype,
which defaults a lead to a big object,
object.prototype,
充满了一些有用的功能。
full of somewhat, useful functions.
我们可以通过用户功能存储的原始属性访问它，链接就会上升。
We can access it via user function store's
proto property, the chain goes up.